60secondmarketer.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy | 60 Second Marketer @AskJamieTurner

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://60secondmarketer.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

## Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

## Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

## Contact forms

## Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Analytics

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## What information do we gather from you?

We collect your name and email when you sign up for any of the free giveaways in the form of ebooks, documents, guides, checklists.

We collect non-identifiable personal information using “cookies.” A cookie is a small data file that a website can transfer to your hard drive through your browser. The cookie is then stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer, but not you. You can set your browser to notify you if cookies are received, or set up your browser to not accept cookies. If you set your browser to block cookies, it may interfere with your ability to use our website to schedule appointments. 

We may collect some other personally identifying information about your use of our website in a non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information, to be analyzed only at an aggregate level for marketing purposes.

## How do we use your information?

We use your name and email to send you the specific information and/or program you have requested. We may use your name and email to send you marketing information and news.

We use first-party and third-party cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we can optimize our website and create a better user experience for you. We may use cookies via Google Analytics Advertising Features, Facebook Advertising, Twitter Advertising, LinkedIn Advertising, Pinterest Advertising, and YouTube Advertising for remarketing, impression reporting, and interest reporting. 

Click here to[ opt-out of Google Analytics cookies](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). If you want to block cookies completely, you can disable them in your browser:[ Chrome](http://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en),[ Firefox](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences),[ Safari](http://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265), or[ Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies). As stated above, if you set your browser to block cookies, it may interfere with your ability to use our shopping cart, make purchases, or use the membership system section of the website.

We do not respond to DNT (“Do Not Track”) privacy settings in your website browser. We may use third-party tracking services to provide data to optimize the services available on this website.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers, and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.  

## How do you unsubscribe, correct, update, review, or delete your information

You can unsubscribe to any email by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. Our data retention policy is that you have control over us deleting your data; in other words, we will keep your data until you tell us to delete it.

## How do we protect your information?

All information gathered on behalf of the 60 Second Marketer is kept strictly confidential and is not sold or rented to any other company in any fashion. Information provided will be used solely to determine and send appropriate information about services or products.

The 60 Second Marketer, a division of SIXTY, LLC is located in the United States and any data you submit will be transferred to the United States. 

We may use the following third parties to help us provide services to you: GetResponse, Zoom and GoToWebinar. These third parties we may use to host your data will keep your data confidential according to their own Privacy Policies.

## Akismet

We collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

## Changes to our privacy policy

 ****Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.
